<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<records>
    <record>
        <url>https://hq-stg.pwc.com/news/archive/26286.html</url>
        <lastModified>Jul 03, 2019 17:30:45</lastModified>
        <pwc_title>Our purpose in action: Protecting trust in the firm in the midst of di</pwc_title>
        <pwc_description></pwc_descriptio>
        <pwc_body>
                Our purpose in action: Protecting trust in the firm in the midst of disaster
    Responsible Business Leadership

    
        Feb. 23, 2018

    




        
        
    

    
        
            
            
            
        
    
    
    


    



    


    



    After 23 years in Tampa, Wendy Steinbacher recently moved to Western North Carolina, near Asheville. Little did she know that her move would lead to a defining moment for her career and for the firm.
 
When Hurricane Irma hit Florida’s West Coast, Wendy was the only member of the US-based Americas IT customer support Help Desk team who wasn’t living in the area -- so it was up to her to solve the problems that arose as a result of the storm.
 
Here’s more from Wendy:
 
Tell us a little bit about your current role at PwC.
I’m a member of the Americas IT organization, which supports our IT infrastructure and firm applications across the US, Canada, Brazil, the Caribbean and some of Latin America. I’m on the IT Customer Support team, which means I’m on the front line of helping our people address their IT issues. I’ve been with the help desk for nine years.
 
What was Hurricane Irma like for you?
In the lead up to the storm, the path of the hurricane started moving west, and we realized it had the potential to impact the Tampa ESC, where my entire US team is based, along with the IT headquarters. Everyone was understandably preparing for the storm, and I was in North Carolina. I told them, “Go take care of your families and your homes, and I’ll take care of the help desk.”
 
On Saturday, PwC Security called the help desk with a problem: They didn’t have the capacity to handle the number of calls they anticipated from staff and partners seeking help. I worked all day Saturday, Saturday night and into Sunday in collaboration with our offshore team to come up with a solution that would allow calls to be routed to more than one person at a time. On Sunday morning, I trained Lisette Martinez, a member of our PwC Security team, on the new solution, just as the storm was beginning to hit Florida in full force.
 
But there was more to come -- on Sunday night the power went out in the Tampa ESC, disrupting call routing for various call centers. I woke up Monday morning to find that the emergency hotline calls were not going to route as planned at the scheduled time. After I notified the appropriate leaders about the issue, the IT Help Desk was asked to take the calls for the Emergency Hotline. I immediately began training our offshore center, who had never taken emergency hotline calls. We got the calls rerouted there so that we could continue to offer critical support to our people, who were calling in with requests for everything from back-up generators to temporary housing, in the middle of one of the worst natural disasters any of them had ever experienced.
 
During the storm, I took on a broader role -- supporting PwC Security in whatever they needed. It became a “Do whatever you have to do” situation. We ended up fielding about 200 calls to the hotline related to Hurricane Irma, and every single one of them was able to get through, despite the problems we were dealing with behind the scenes.
 
Looking back at the experience, how did you demonstrate our purpose in your response?
A lot of it was about trust -- people trust that the firm will be there for them in times of incredible need. It’s one of the things that makes us special. People can’t call the emergency hotline during a hurricane and get a busy signal or a “Sorry, your call can’t be answered at this time.” It just can’t happen. So we had to think outside the box, and do things we hadn’t done before, and that definitely made me feel like I was solving an important problem.
 
How did this experience help you find meaning in your work?
Working on the help desk, I don’t always get to see the immediate impact of what I do every day, because so much happens behind the scenes. We work hard every day to meet the expectations of the firm, but if we are doing our job well, things are running smoothly and it may not even be noticed. With a situation like this, I could see the direct and immediate impact of what I was working on, and it was really energizing to see how my experience and skills helped me create quick workarounds in this high-pressure situation. I had a purpose, and that purpose was to ensure there was no downtime, no impact and no bad experience for anyone being affected by Irma. The commitment the firm has made that the emergency hotline would be there for partners and staff, no matter what -- delivering on that was my purpose.
 
It doesn’t take a natural disaster to be a hero. Whether we’re conducting a forensics investigation, implementing a new technology or helping clients navigate a merger, people place their trust in us when the stakes are high.
 
No matter what our role, we all have opportunities to go above and beyond to deliver our work and find meaning in what we do every day. How does our purpose resonate with you? Share your stories with us!
 
To learn more about purpose at PwC, visit our Purpose Spark page.
 

Wendy (third from right) and members of her team at a recent training event.



    



    




    
    
     Top News 
    

    


    


    




    
    

    


    







            
    
    

    
    






    

    

    




            

        
        
          
        
        
        
        
    


</pwc_body>
    </record>
    <record>
        <url>https://hq-stg.pwc.com/news/archive/26611.html</url>
        <lastModified>Jul 03, 2019 17:30:45</lastModified>
        <pwc_title>Managing your energy on the road: How to keep your batteries charged</pwc_title>
        <pwc_description></pwc_description>
        <pwc_body>
    
    
    
    
        
        
            



            
 


 




    
    


    
    

    




    
    


    
    
    
        
        
            
                Managing your energy on the road: How to keep your batteries charged
            
        
        
        




    People Team

    
        March 6, 2018

    




        
        
    

    
        
            
            
            
        
    
    
    


    



    


    



    Traveling can be stressful. It also can lead to poor eating habits, sleep deprivation or lack of exercise. Want some remedies? See these 20 tips that cover all four dimensions of energy to make sure you stay on track while on the road. 
Physical


Establish a bedtime routine specifically for when you travel (pre-trip, during the trip, on return).
Find healthy food options before you arrive at your destination.
Research hotel fitness options and create a workout plan.
Schedule your day in 90-minute sprints with clear finish lines.
Declare a specific end to your work day and stick to it.

Emotional


Talk to others on the road or at home about the interesting or positive experiences of traveling.
Call or leave a video message for a loved one each morning/evening. 
Schedule time in your travel schedule for the things you enjoy most.
Send a note to someone you appreciate, making sure to be specific about why you appreciate them.
Load your phone with photos of enjoyable experiences you’ve had recently, music or podcasts you can escape into. 
 

Mental


Create a packing list you can refer to every trip. Download Packing Pro and other travel apps from PwC’s App Store.
Create a priority list in advance with key colleagues and clients you plan to meet.
Block 30-90 minutes at the start of the day for your first commitment.
Build in downtime to your schedule where you’re completely disconnected from work.
Establish a reflection journal to note how you’re managing energy on the road. Share with your team at your next meeting.
 

Spirtual


Pack your purpose (discuss this with someone who knows you well).
Book your return flight at a reasonable time.
Make time for yourself at some point during the day. For example, meditate or read a few pages of your book. 
Pack items that remind you of what's important.
Look for opportunities to volunteer in the areas you’re traveling to.
 

Check out these learning assets in Vantage too:

Well-being tips at the client site
5 mindfulness travel hacks for the road warrior
 

We are just over a month into The habit challenge. And don't forget the Your Tomorrow, Our Time Off challenge -- if we meet our goals, we’ll get the entire July 4 week off! For the Be well, work well component, 90% of us must do three things: 
 

Take the Energy Audit
Visit the Habit Bank
Be part of at least one Be well, work well team plan

We are just over a month into The habit challenge. Do you have tips or best practices? Share with the Be well, work well team. 

After a long week, two members of Team on a Com(mission) catch some z’s on an earlier flight home one Friday.
"This work also includes © copyrighted materials of Resync Inc. d/b/a The Energy Project. All rights are reserved."




    



    




    
    
     Top News 
    

    


    


    




    
    

    


    







            
    
    

    
    






    

    

    




            

        
        
          
        
        
        
        
    
</pwc_body>
    </record>
    <record>
        <url>https://hq-stg.pwc.com/pages/about-hq/hq-faqs.html</url>
        <lastModified>Jul 03, 2019 17:30:45</lastModified>
        <pwc_title>HQ FAQs</pwc_title>
        <pwc_description>Get started with HQ! Learn more about this exciting platform with a list of frequently asked questions.</pwc_description>
        <pwc_body>
    
    
    
    
        
        
            



            
 


 




    
    


    
    

    




    
    


    
    

    
        
            
            
            
        
        General Information

What is HQ?
HQ is the Firm's new intranet platform, replacing myKcurve, PwC's legacy intranet of more than 10 years. This new site, powered by Adobe Experience Manager, further drives our Your Tomorrow strategy by serving as a modern, personalized portal that's your front door to firmwide and LoS news, tools and resources.
PwC HQ is designed to give you easier access to the information you need to work, day in and day out. The user-friendly interface thoughtfully streamlines navigation and content so that you have on-demand access to the top apps and sites that you use on a daily basis.

Fun fact: the name HQ (an abbreviation for headquarters) was chosen by our partners and staff back in January when we launched a survey to choose the name for our new intranet. Over 6,400 of you voted on the first piece of bringing this new site to life!
For more information, refer to the About HQ page.
What are some of the key features of HQ?

The first release of HQ is called an “MVP - Minimum Viable Product” launch, which means that this is just the beginning and HQ will continue to be enhanced in the coming months. The following features are currently included:

New look and feel, mobile-friendly user experience

Streamlined navigation (fewer navigation items, more intuitive ways to get to underlying content, customizable Quick Links)

Personalization (content across the site is targeted according to your personal attributes e.g. LoS, Sector, location)

Key Dates (see upcoming firmwide events and add them to your Google calendar with one click)


Stay tuned for more information on future enhancements.
What will be included in future releases?

Our HQ roadmap will continue to be refined and grow in the coming months. Right now, key items for our product roadmap include:

Integrate predictive data and insights from the new myMetrics; Astro alignment

Integrate key sites and systems into HQ search (align with enterprise search/Fathom on the front end)

Expand personalization/preferences and analytics

Mexico portal migration (via Spark)

Partner Portal evaluation and approach

Email/newsletter solution alignment and integration

Collaboration platform alignment


Is myKcurve going away?

The front-end staff experience of myKcurve will no longer be available. However, the partner portal, also on Kcurve, will not be turned off in June and will be available to partners through personalized navigation.
Is HQ available on mobile?

The first release is "mobile-responsive."  Post MVP, we will move towards "mobile-native," or an experience that can be fully realized in app format (with app notifications).
Will HQ have social and/or collaboration functionality?

You will have the ability to share content from HQ with other partners and staff. More community functionality (commenting and liking, for example) will be introduced in future releases of HQ.
The US firm is currently exploring options for firmwide collaboration tools. Once that decision has been made, the approved solution for collaboration may be integrated into the HQ experience.

Is HQ replacing Spark?

No, HQ is not replacing Spark. The firm is in the process of reviewing collaboration and self-service web creation tools that will support the future demands of our Your Tomorrow agenda, but for now, we will still use Spark. With that said, there is content on Spark that is integral to our new digital workplace experience -- content that represents our firm strategy, structure and values -- that we will evaluate and update for potential migration onto HQ.
Is HQ available in Mexico?

The Mexico portal experience will remain on Spark in the near-term but we are looking to migrate it to HQ in FY20.
Is HQ available to contractors or employees outside the US?

Our contractor and PwC global employees will not have the personalization features in HQ that are available to our US employees (as these are pulled from Workday), but they will be able to view the content.
How can I personalize my HQ experience?

On Day 1, you can enhance your HQ experience by populating your Quick Links and ensuring that your personalization settings are properly set.  The personal attributes (according to Workday) that will inform the content that you see in your homepage news feed and suggested Quick Links are: line of service, sector/subsector and location.  You can see the attributes from your Workday profile by clicking the person link in the top right corner of your HQ screen.
How can I find information outside of my personalized areas?

If you are looking for content that isn’t personalized to you (e.g., you’re in Advisory and looking for information or news from Assurance), use Search and then filter by any LoS. In the future, we will be adding additional personalization features and you will also have the ability to subscribe to news from other lines of service, sectors and locations.  
How can I customize my Quick Links?

Quick Links are designed to give you one-click access to the sites and systems you frequent most (see visual here). You have ten Quick Links available in your left hand navigation. Four of those ten Quick Links have been pre-populated based on your role at the firm, e.g., Tax Source for a Tax employee, or Consulting Source for an Advisory employee.
All Quick Links can be edited, including the ones that are pre-populated.  Staff can choose Quick Links by selecting the HQ Link Index, which will open an index of ~400 sites and systems that staff frequent most.  You can add or remove a Quick Link by selecting the + or - button to the right of the link in the Link Index.

How can I find my LoS/function information?

You will see personalized news appear on the HQ homepage, specific to your LoS, sector and location. LoS communications and change teams will continue to create and publish content. In addition, you can find the LOS homepages in the “Our Clients and Business” navigation menu and these pages will link out to other areas.
How can I provide feedback on HQ?

Visit the HQ feedback community to share your ideas for product enhancements, see what others have suggested and vote on the ideas you’d like to see come to life. Your participation in this feedback tool will help the HQ team identify and prioritize enhancements to the site’s user experience, influencing the site’s user experience and product roadmap.
How can I search on HQ?

HQ makes it easier to access the information you need to deliver for our clients and our firm, and do so more efficiently. The HQ search functionality is a simplified experience that provides a single search bar, instead of the toggle search functionality available previously on myKcurve. Therefore, HQ search results will only display content (i.e., pages, microsites) and news (firmwide and LoS) that are native to HQ and will not surface all results from the sources that could be found on the myKcurve search bar (e.g., Fathom, A&quot;A, Tax Source). Over time, HQ search will become more robust as we integrate with other platforms.
Please stay tuned for updates on the timing of these, and other, HQ enhancements. In the meantime, access to individual search repositories, including Fathom, Aquot;A and Tax Source, can be added as Quick Links or found in the Link Index.
Will I be able to set reminders of my own on HQ?

Yes, you can add certain firmwide key dates to your calendar. Navigate to the “Key Dates” section of HQ and click the “add to calendar” icon for available events. Once Astro, PwC’s cognitive agent, is launched firmwide, we will add the ability for you to see a more personalized list of “To Dos,” including a view of any tasks that you’ve set in Google Tasks and those added via Astro.
How can I request new pages to be added to HQ?
If you’d like to develop a new HQ page or migrate a site from another platform into HQ, please  contact the HQ Team.
Where do I go if I experience issues with HQ?
If you have general questions/ comments about your HQ experience or need feedback community support, contact the HQ Team. For technical assistance with HQ (e.g., report bugs, personalization settings not working), please submit a request through Service Hub.



    



    




    
    

    Need additional help?
Tech support

HQ bugs and requests for technology support should be directed to Service Hub.
Requests for content
To request new HQ content/pages or changes to existing content/pages, please contact the HQ Team.
Feedback

Visit the HQ feedback community to share your ideas for product enhancements, see what others have suggested and vote on the ideas you’d like to see come to life.



    



    


    




    
    
    
        
    
    
    
        Have feedback? Let us know what you think.
        Share your suggestions
    



    


    







            
    
    

    
    






    

    

    




            

        
        
          
        
        
        
        
    

</pwc_body>
    </record>
        <record>
        <url>https://hq-stg.pwc.com/news/firmwide/partner-executive-comms/uslt-fy20-update.html</url>
        <lastModified>Jul 03, 2019 17:30:45</lastModified>
        <pwc_title>3 new members of the US Leadership Team for FY20</pwc_title>
        <pwc_description></pwc_description>
        <pwc_body>    
    
    
    
        
        
            



            
 


 




    
    


    
    

    




    
    


    
    
    
        
        
            
                3 new members of the US Leadership Team for FY20
            
        
        
        




    Tim Ryan

    
        June 25, 2019

    
        by Tim Ryan
    




        
        
    

    
        
            
            
            
        
    
    
    


    



    


    



    Team:
I’m proud and excited to update you on several partners who will be joining the US Leadership Team (USLT) in FY20. Shannon Schuyler, Farhad Zaman and Wes Bricker will be joining the USLT, bringing new perspectives and experiences to the team.

For those who are new to the firm, the USLT has management responsibility for our business and for driving our strategy with speed and agility. We work on behalf of all of you to make choices for our firm and to keep our business strong for the long term. Shannon, Farhad and Wes will immediately begin working with the rest of the team to drive and execute our strategy.

The USLT is representative of the tremendous diversity and talent within our firm and brings many different skill sets, experiences and ways of thinking to the table.



    




    
        
            
            
            
        
    
    
    


    



    Wes will step into the role of Assurance Leader, succeeding Maria Moats.  Maria has led the Assurance practice through a very important period of change and innovation. Wes will help us keep our momentum and build on all that has been done to enhance audit quality, advance innovation and run our business well. Wes is a former PwC Assurance partner. He left the firm and joined the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in 2015 and was named SEC Chief Accountant in 2016. Wes has resigned from his role at the SEC and is returning as an Assurance partner, based in the Washington D.C. area.
Shannon will serve as Chief Purpose and Inclusion Officer with responsibility for both the Office of Diversity &quot; Inclusion and Responsible Business Leadership. Shannon is a proven leader committed to meaningful change and action that drives connectivity, engagement and pride in the work we do together. Shannon will bring unique insights and perspectives from her existing roles as Chief Purpose Officer and Responsible Business Leader to the Chief Diversity Officer role. As she transitions into this role, Shannon will work closely with Mike Dillon, who has championed the importance of diversity and inclusion as a business imperative for the past three years. 
Farhad will serve as Chief Network Officer for the US, succeeding Suneet Dua. Farhad was born in Bangladesh and grew up in seven countries on five continents before joining the firm. He has 26 years of extensive international experience serving many of our global Fortune 100 clients as a Deals partner and through overseas secondments with PwC Australia, India and UK. In his 14 years as a partner, Farhad’s roles have included National Office partner, human capital leader for CMAAS and the US Capital Markets leader. As Farhad moves into this role, Suneet will be refocusing his time on Your Tomorrow as a service offering for clients.

Team, we’re fortunate to be part of a firm that provides us with so many opportunities for growth and success. I know you will join me in congratulating and supporting all those taking on new responsibilities. And please also join me in thanking Maria, Mike and Suneet for the hard work and leadership they have demonstrated over the past three years as part of the US Leadership Team.



    




    
        
            
            
            
        
    
    
    


    



    Contact: us_hq_news@pwc.com



    



    




    
    
     Top News 
    

    


    


    




    
    

    


    







            
    
    

    
    






    

    

    




            

        
        
          
        
        
        
        
    

</pwc_body>
    </record>
    <record>
        <url>https://hq-stg.pwc.com/quick-links/advisory-national-pursuit-team.html</url>
        <lastModified>Jul 03, 2019 17:30:45</lastModified>
        <pwc_title>Advisory National Pursuit Team</pwc_title>
        <pwc_description>Advisory NPT supports the largest pursuits in the practice nationally, as well as smaller but strategically important opportunities.</pwc_description>
        <pwc_body></pwc_body>
    </record>
</records>
